[{"question": "The dot product of 2 vectors will be ", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "a scalar", "correct": true}, {"answer": "a vector", "correct": false}, {"answer": "2 vectors", "correct": false}, {"answer": "2 scalars", "correct": false}], "tag": "dot_product applications", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "When evaluating line integrals, we need to be cautious of choosing the parameterization of the curve in order to get the right solution", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Yes, the solution to a line integral will depend on the curve parameterization.", "correct": false}, {"answer": "No, we can choose any form of parameterization and will reach the same solution.", "correct": true}, {"answer": "-", "correct": false}, {"answer": "-", "correct": false}], "tag": "line_integral applications", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "Using lagrange multipliers to find a local optimum ", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Eliminates constraint equations", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Uses gradients to locate the optimum", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Modifies the objective function", "correct": false}, {"answer": "All of the above", "correct": true}], "tag": "lagrange_multipliers applications", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "What is the relation between a Jacobian J and a Hessian H of a function f(x)", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "J = H( gradient(f(x)))", "correct": false}, {"answer": "H = gradient (J(f(x))", "correct": false}, {"answer": "H = J( gradient (f(x)))", "correct": true}, {"answer": "There is no relation", "correct": false}], "tag": "jacobian hessian derivative", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "Which of the following is not an implicit function", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "sin(x)  + sin^2(y) = 0.75", "correct": false}, {"answer": "3x^2 - 10 = y", "correct": true}, {"answer": "y^4 + x^3 = 8", "correct": false}, {"answer": "x^2 = y^2 - 10", "correct": false}], "tag": "implicit_function applications", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "<p>The correct function call to grad() for evaluating the partial derivative with respect to x2 is:</p>\n<pre><code class=\"language-python\">def f(x1, x2, x3):\n    return x1^2 + x2^2 -x3^3\n</code></pre>", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "grad(f, x2)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "grad(f, 0)", "correct": false}, {"answer": "grad(f, 1)", "correct": true}, {"answer": "grad(f, 2)", "correct": false}], "tag": "autograd derivative", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "Automatic differentiation can be used for", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Constrained Optimization", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Line integrals", "correct": false}, {"answer": "Sensitivity Analysis", "correct": false}, {"answer": "All of the above", "correct": true}], "tag": "automatic_differentiation derivative", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "Which of the following is not an implicit function", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "x^2 + 2x - 5 - y^2 = 0", "correct": false}, {"answer": "x^2 - 5 = y^2", "correct": false}, {"answer": "xy = x + y", "correct": true}, {"answer": "sin(x)  + sin^2(y) = 0.75", "correct": false}], "tag": "implicit_function applications", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "To calculate how a variable changes with respect to a certain parameter, we can use", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "Partial derivative of the variable with respect to the parameter", "correct": true}, {"answer": "There are only experimental approaches to achieve this", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A change of basis", "correct": false}, {"answer": "A total derivative with respect to time", "correct": false}], "tag": "derivative", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}, {"question": "What is the partial derivative of the function f(x, y, z) = x^2 * e^z * cos(y) + 2*z*x*y, with respect to z.", "type": "multiple_choice", "answers": [{"answer": "x^2 * cos(y) + 2*y*x", "correct": false}, {"answer": "x^2 * e^z * cos(y) + 2*y*x", "correct": true}, {"answer": "2*y*x", "correct": false}, {"answer": "x^2 * e^z * cos(y) + 2*x*y*z", "correct": false}], "tag": "derivative", "lecture_file": "20_autograd_applications"}]